Preliminary Inventory to the Metropolitan Council on Housing Records TAM.173
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series III. 2002 Accession and Subsequent Accessions through 2007, 39.0 linear feet
  - Shelter Force: Tenants' History Project, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Small Building Committee, 1980s (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Spanish Language articles, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - The Tenant readers' survey, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Publicity workshops, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Tenant Emancipation Rally, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Radio and TV records, 1967-1975 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - WBAI programs, "Rent and Housing", 1969-1974 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Rockaway Low-income Housing Proposal, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Riverwalk, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Riverton, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Riverside South, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Resolution Trust Corporation, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Rent Strike Guide, undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Rockefeller University: Landlord, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Roosevelt Hospital: Landlord, undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Save Our Cities March, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Northern Students Movement, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - National Housing Law Project, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Rooming Houses, undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - SROs, undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Lofts, undated (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Relocation, undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Housing Justice Campaign, undated (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Ziman v. Division of Housing and Community Renewal (DHCR), undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Federal Housing, undated (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - MCH: Senior Campaigns, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Rent Guidelines Board, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Tenant/Inquilino article on vacancy rate, Mar 1998 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - MCH statements, 1960s-1970s (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Site Action Minutes, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Spring Beautification Project - Site Action, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Mothers Against Drugs Site Action / War on Drugs, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Site Action/Minutes, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - East Third Street Playground, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Site Action/Religious groups/War on Drugs, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Site Action/Flyers, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Blank letterhead paper, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Cooper Square, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - 3 Kings Flyer Denis Oliver, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Block Captain Network, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Site Action/War on Drugs, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Cooper Square Newsletter, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Privat, undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - 7 Second Avenue, undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Joint Planning Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Strategy Committee, undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - 7 East Third Street, undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - 9 East Third Street, undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - 21 East Third Street, undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - 23 East Third Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - 23 East Third Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - 25 East Third Street, undated (Box 46, Folder S3)
  - 27 East Third Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 56 East Fourth Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - 60 East Fourth Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - 65 East Fourth Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - 65 East Fourth Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - 65 East Fourth Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - 63 East Fourth Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - 63 East Fourth Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - 63 East Fourth Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - 57 East Fourth Street, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Cooper Square Committee files, 1970s (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Square Committee files;Chinese Preservation meeting;Spanish Preservation meeting;Site Action, 1970s (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Housing Code Enforcement, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Of interest to arts committee, undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Arts Committee of Cooper Square, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Cooper Square artists interview, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Old list of site artists, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Artists' statements (August 13, 1969 to February 13, 1970), 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Cooper Square Committee: SOHO: Loft conversion, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Westbeth, undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Cooper Square Committee: La Mama, undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Cooper Square Committee: National Register of Historic Places, undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Cooper Square Committee: National Trust, undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Blank Survey: CETA, undated (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Landmarks Conservancy, undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Landmarks: Survey/Information, undated (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Cooper Square Committee: NY Council for the Humanities, undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Building Structure Inventory Forms, undated (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Historical Research Forms, undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Cooper Square Committee: New Wilderness Foundation, undated (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Inner City Ventures Fund Preliminary Application, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Attachments, undated (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Negotiating Committee, 1990-1998 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Cooper Square Plans 1969-1982, undated (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Police permits: Blanks, receipts and copies, 1964-1970, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Rehabilitation survey, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Public housing: Cooper Square, 1963-1970 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Letter re: Rental agreements, filled vacancies, May 17, 1971, May 1971 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Rent Strike Material: 23 East Third Street, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Resumes for Cooper Square, 1970-1971 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Steering Committee minutes, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Reports to the Steering Committee, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Steering Committee minutes, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Steering Committee reports, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Cooper Square Community Development Committee: Minutes and other documents, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Outgoing Mail, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Incoming Mail, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Steering Committee minutes, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - Unorganized Cooper Square Committee documents, including:PhotographsCooper Square Committee Steering Committee election ballots (1984, 1987, 1992)CSC Neighborhood Preservation Program (2000)Financial statements (2000)Staff attendance books (1981-2000)Cooper Square Committee publications: Thelma Burdick: From the Heart(1990) Cooper Square Committee Forty-Fifth Anniversary and Gala, 1959-2004 (2004) Cooper Square Committee "housewarming" party(2005) Cooper Square Committee Chronology(2005), 1981-2005 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Security posters (Spanish and English) and anything else about security (memos, etc.), undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Security deposits action, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Site action minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Site office, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Site occupancy record cards, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Simon's group, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Show cause order (CPC), undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Third Avenue Rezoning, 1969-1970 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Thirteenth Street Squatters, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Traffic Department, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Trees, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Al Upton, 95 East Houston Street, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Urban Development Corporation (UDC), undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Coastal Properties, undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Blanks, undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Program survey, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Cooper Square Committee documents, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Pagan's Girls Club, undated (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Dutch Interns, undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - ANHD / Housing Justice Campaign / 236 West Twenty-Seventh Street, undated (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - 13 East Third Street, undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Hernandez, William: 60 East Fourth Street, Apartment 2, undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Cooper Square Budget, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Salvation Army Drop-in Center, undated (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Cooper Square Membership Meeting (November 30, 1994), Nov 1994 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Lower East Side Squatters: Garden of Eden, undated (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Community Access, undated (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Pagan, Antonio, undated (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - M. of A.: Methodist, Sponsorship, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Song Sheets, undated (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Esperanza, 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Official Documents (January 7, 1970), Jan 1970 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Stage 1 Plans, undated (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Di Donato, Luigi, 1967-1968 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Courthouse Site, 1968-1971 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - CURMCO, undated (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Davis, Edmond, Attorney-at-law, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Housing and Development Authority, 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Cooper Square: Tenant's application for decrease in rent (32-4-S), undated (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Letter to New York Times(July 19, 1971), Jul 1971 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Early Action Program Planning, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Welfare Advice, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Tenant Information, undated (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Tenant Compliance Committee, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - Tenant Committee for Fourth Street, undated (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Squatters, undated (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - Stage 1, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Statistical breakdown for Urban Development Corporation (UDC), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Women's Building, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - St. Mark's Committee, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - St. Mark's building analysis, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - Sponsors: Building, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - De Salvio, Louis, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - Digest: Alternate plan, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - Rent strike: 23 East Third Street, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Survey data, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - Statements on Cooper Square, 1963-1964 (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Special events, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - Statements at hearings, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Documents from city housing agencies, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - Press clippings and releases, 1966-1970 (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - Dispossess Notices, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Thirty day notice, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Tenants paying increases, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Petitions re: Commercial rent increase, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Rent increase survey and fact sheet, Sep 1977 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Cooper Square election material, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Barretto, Carmen, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Subway passes, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Pohani Association, Inc., undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Assets Consulting Group, undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Bank resolutions, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Thelma Burdick Tenants / Hall rental, undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Summer festival, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Bank resolution, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Site Action minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Support services: Cube Building, undated (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - William Viera, undated (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Steering Committee correspondence, undated (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Cube Building watch, undated (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Cube work, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Cooper Square Committee, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Cooper Square Committee and Cooper Square Mutual Housing Association relations, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Bank resolution, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Program (NPP) Financial Report, 1989-1993 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Program (NPP) Financial Report, 1993-1995 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Program (NPP) Financial Report, 1995-1996 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Program (NPP) Financial Report, 1999-2002 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Board (Cooper Square Committee Steering Committee) minutes, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Housing Preservation and Development (HPD), 2000 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Computer repairs, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Jobs Fair Expenses, Insurance, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Bank resolutions: Forms and draft, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Bell Atlantic: Bonus statements, undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Payroll and timesheets, undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Bank resolution, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Bank resolution, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Legalization of tenants, undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Memos from coordinating meetings/Daniel Grulich, undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Construction Monitor contract, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Mutual Housing Association meeting minutes, undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Supers, undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Supers, undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Low flush toilets, undated (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Fuller/PRC Construction, undated (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Masonry Specs Site 4 and 5, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Rehabilitation process, undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Mutual Housing Association, undated (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Management Company, undated (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Proposed budget for Cooper Square Mutual Housing Association, undated (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Relocation resources: Off/On site, undated (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Apartments, vacant: Legal cases, Nov 1990 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Residential/commercial tenants, undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Criteria for legalization, undated (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Relocated tenants, undated (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - 58 and 60 East Fourth Street (September 11, 1991), Sep 1991 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Damp/Apartment surveys, undated (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Tenant profiles (needs), undated (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Phasing of rehabilitation (Mutual Housing Association), undated (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Meeting with Stiller (March 6, 1993), Mar 1993 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Cooper Square Committee files and non-filed documents, including:Steering Committee minutes (1980s)Public Housing Speak-Out (April 26, 1997)Cooper Square Committee meetingsQuality housing zoning regulationsNew Plan for Cooper SquareHousing Preservation and Development (HPD) Urban Renewal Area Survey, 1980s-1990s (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Square Committee files and non-filed documents, including:Steering Committee minutes and reports (1973-1976)Mutual Housing Association documents (1980s), 1973-1976, 1980s (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Square Committee documents, including: Steering Committee minutes and reports, 1973-1983 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Square Committee documents, including: Steering Committee minutes and reports (1984-1989)Membership Committee election material (1980s) (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - MCH and Cooper Square Committee files, including:Cooper Square Committee Steering Committee Elections: June 26, 1986 and May 25, 1988Employee evaluations and personnel documents (1980s), 1970s-1980s (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Cooper Square Committee Steering Committee Director's File, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Cooper Square Committee Steering Committee Elections (June 26, 1986) (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Cooper Square Committee Steering Committee Elections (May 25, 1988) (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Housing Preservation and Development (HPD) Community Consultant Program (October 1986 to June 1987), 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - House Personnel, undated (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - House Personnel, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Arts Committee, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Stripping, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Meeting with Housing Preservation and Development (HPD) Central Office, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - House Personnel and Staff Meetings, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Grant proposals for summer festival, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter copy Volume 4, Number 2, Mar 1979 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Rental agreement and relevant correspondence, undated (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing correspondence with Commissioner Nathan Leventhal, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Leaflets, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Housing Preservation and Development (HPD) Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Joint Planning Council (JPC) Literature, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Estimate for sealing, 71 East Fourth Street, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - To be read, undated (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Cube, undated (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Joint Planning Council (JPC), undated (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Lower East Side tour, undated (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - National Cooperative Bank, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Cooper Square Plan news articles, undated (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - AT&T Phone Service, undated (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Cooper Square Committee Steering Committee minutes, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Cooper Square Committee Steering Committee minutes, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - HUD Section S Regulations, undated (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Unidentified file, undated (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Unidentified Cooper Square Committee file, undated (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Senior Affairs Committee, undated (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Membership letter (Spanish), undated (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Membership letter (English), undated (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Files and unfiled documents, including:Meeting minutesOddlettes, etc.Cube buildingSteering CommitteeCooper Square CommitteeMutual Housing Authority (MHA) Buildings29 East Second StreetNon-MHA buildings59-61 East Fourth StreetCooper UnionFloor plansGLM information, 1980s-1990s (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Unfiled documents and files including:News clippings and leaflets (1965)PhotographsStaff Manual, 1960s (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Cooper Square Committee: Unfiled documents, 1970s-1990s (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Series IV: 2008 Accession., 8.0 linear feet
  This series contains subject and administrative files relating to the themes covered in Series I and II; topics and organizations most prominently represented include the Division of Housing and Community Renewal, rent control and rent stabilization, co-op conversions, and lobbying activity in Albany, New York.
  - Albany, 1989-1991 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Albany, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Albany Lobby Day, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Albany Legislation, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - City Council Legislation, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - City Owned Building, 1970-1977 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Cuomo Campaign, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Dinkins, 1986-1991 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Disabled Coalition NYC/Coalition for Housing for Disabled People, 1980-1987 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Energy, 1977-1983 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Evictions, 1975-1993 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Evictions, 1984-1986 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Fair Housing, 1961-1984 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Handicapped, 1974-1990 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - In REM, 1978-1982 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - In REM, 1978-1985 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - In REM HPD (city owned building), 1970-1985 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - In REM HPD (city owned building), 1980-1983 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - In REM Legislation, 1978-1982 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Legislative, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Park Conservation, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Pataki, 1994-2003 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Racism, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Racism/Segregation, 1964-1973 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Rent Stabilization Code Revision, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Starret City, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Tenants Unity Coalition, 1987-1988 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Tenants Unity Coalition, 1989-1992 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Views Harlem Parents Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Waterside Housing Development, 1967-1975 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Williamsburg, 1961-1963 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - 48th District Election, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Annadale Hugenont, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Berkeley Rent Control Decision, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Commercial rent Regulation, 1971-1985 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Cooper Square Project Dilemma, 1986-2002 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Federal Housing Policy Regulation #403, 1975-1977 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Federal Rent Guidelines, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Fuel Cost Adjustment, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Fuel Costs (I), 1979-1989 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Fuel Costs (II), 1990 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Garrison Pataki Demonstration, 2002-2004 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Housing Politics and Theory, 1986-1991 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Housing Rehabilitation, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Housing Vacancy Survey, 1981-2001 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Lower East Side Joint Planning, 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - MBR, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - MBR, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - MBR (I), 1997 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - MBR (II), 1997 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - MBR, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - MBR, 2000-2001 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - MBR, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - MBR Campaign, Nov 1995 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - MBR Fall, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1961-2003 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - News and Press Releases, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Political Action Committee, 1995-1998 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Property Tax, 1987-2003 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Public Housing, 1967-1997 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Redlining, 1974-1976 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Relocation, 1962-1980 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Rent Guidelines Board, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Rent Guidelines Board Rent Formulas, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Rent Laws, 1999-2003 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Rent Laws (City), 1994 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Rent Regulations, 1994-1996 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - 575 Hancock St., undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Albany, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Albany, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Albany, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Albany, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Albany Tenant Unity Coalition, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Anti-unauthorized Occupant Campaign, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Appleby, Thomas, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Barbaro, Frank, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Bell Park Gardens, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Breezy Point, 1962-1968 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Brown, Rick, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Bumpers, Eleanor, 1984-1987 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Citizens Housing and Planning Council, 1972-1985 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Cohn, Roy, 1951-1969 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Columbia University Evictions, 1975-1989 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Community Resource Exchange, undated (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Cuomo, Andrew, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Damato, Al, 1981-1997 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Economics of Real Estate, 1977-1980 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Evans, Lester, 1976-1987 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Fair Housing/March For Jobs And Freedom, 1963-1967 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Gray, Jesse, 1985-1988 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Green, Mark, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Homesteading, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Housing and Development Administration Reorganization, 1975-1977 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Kamiat, Edith, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - La Larouche, 1970-1997 (Box 64, Folder 33)